

# Vo Hoai Son

**Date of Birth:** 06/10/1996

**Phone:** 0974 105 003

Email: vector.mic@gmail.com

**Gender:** Male

Address: Ho Chi Minh

### **DESCRIPTION**

I'm good at JavaScript and related frameworks, My strength is PHP, JavaScript, C#.NET, Node.JS and now I gradually turn into research about Data Mining, Deep Learning and Neural Networks.My hobbies are manga/anime, piano and poetry.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

Oct 2016 – Present

### **GẦN NHÀ**

### **Front-end Developer**

### https://gannha.com/

- Working here as a Front-end Web developer
- Cordova, Ionic, Angular and .NET developer
- Have learned about critical thinking, problem solving and project management
- Improve soft skills in this working environment

Mar 2017 – Aug 2017

#### **AVA LABS TECH**

### A.I. Researcher / Data Scientist

### https://topplayer.co/

- Working as a team leader and product manager
- Machine Learning, Data Mining, Deep Learning and Blockchain
- Have learned about business analytics, administration
- Well-learned about Python and related libraries

Apr 2016 – Jul 2016

#### ZEND.VN

#### **PHP Intern**

### http://zendvn.com/

- Research about VCS: Git, SVN
- Working with PHP Frameworks: CodeIgniter, Zend, Composer

- Well-learned about WordPress CMS
- Do a mockup project: https://batdongsan.com.vn/

### **EDUCATIONS**

2014 – 2018 UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE HO CHI MINH

**Major: Computer Software Engineer** 

### **ACTIVITIES**

Sep 2016 – Present

#### **MICROSOFT STUDENT PARTNERS**

### **Technical Evangelist**

- Organize Microsoft events: Microsoft Academic Tour, Hour of Code, Imagine Cup 2017 to the universities
- Sharing Microsoft technologies: Azure, Xamarin, .NET Core

### **HONORS & AWARDS**

Mar 2017

#### **MICROSOFT IMAGINE CUP 2017**

- Archive 3<sup>rd</sup> place in the Imagine Cup 2017 Vietnam competition
- Project: Pack'nGoTeam: 101studio
- Role: Business Analyzer, .NET Developer, Designer and Video

Editor

### **SKILLS**

Language Vietnamese, English

Skills **PHP**: 7/10

**Node.JS**: 6/10

Angular: 7/10

WordPress: 8/10

## **PROJECTS**

Oct 2016 – Present	GẦN NHÀ
	https://gannha.com/
	<ul> <li>A platform that users can find anything near them with only 3 taps</li> </ul>
	- Building a Admin dashboard using Angular 2
Mar 2017 – Aug 2017	TOPPLAYER
	https://topplayer.co/
	<ul> <li>A platform that matching users with jobs in 1 tap</li> <li>Stack: MongoDB, Angular 2, Python Django Rest Framework, NodeJS</li> </ul>
Jul 2017 – Aug 2017	JANHOME
	https://janhome.vn/
	Building a website using WordPress
Jun 2017 – Jul 2017	TUVANGOICUOC
	https://tuvangoicuoc.com/
	Building a website using WordPress
Sep 2016 – Oct 2016	TROPICAL OCEAN RESORT
	http://tropicaloceanresort.vn/
	Building a website using WordPress
Jul 2016 – Aug 2016	OMWATER
	https://omwater.vn/
	Building a website using WordPress